Finding Aid for the North American New Music Festival Sound Recordings, 1983-1993
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Cassettes, 1983-1993, I.; Cassette 1-390
  - Rorem, Ned, 1923- Cycle of Holy songs (1955), 1993-10-28, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 624 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 357 Side a)
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_357aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_357asc.mp3
  - Horne, David, 1970- Letter (1993), 1993-10-28, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 625 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 357 Side b)
    Performers: Gary Burgess, tenor; David Horne, piano
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_357bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_357bsc.mp3
  - Rorem, Ned, 1923- Santa Fe songs (1980), 1993-10-28, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 626 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 358 Side a)
    Performers: Daniel McCabe, baritone; Thomas Halpin, violin; Valerie Heywood-How, viola; Arie Lipsky, violoncello; Luk', piano
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_358aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_358asc.mp3
  - Wood, James, 1953- Spirit festival with lamentations (1992), 1993-10-29, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 628 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 359 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 188, October 29, 1993, 8:00 p.m.
    Duration: 26:41
    Performers: Percussive Rotterdam
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_359aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_359asc.mp3
  - Klatzow, Peter Dances of earth and fire (1989), 1993-10-29, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 627 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 359 Side b)
    Duration: 13:11
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_359bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_359bsc.mp3
  - Xenakis, Iannis, 1922-2001 Pleiades (1978). Part 1, 1993-10-29, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 629 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 360 Side a)
    Duration: 24:51
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_360aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_360asc.mp3
  - Xenakis, Iannis, 1922-2001 Pleiades (1978). Part 2, 1993-10-29, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 629 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 360 Side b)
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_360bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_360bsc.mp3
  - Cage, John One [to 4th power]; Three [squared]; Four [to 4th power]; Six. Part 1, 1993-10-30, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 630-NAF 633 Tape type: TDK_SA_90 (Box 7, Audiocassette 361 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 190, October 30, 1993, 2:00 p.m.
    Duration: 47:14
    The four works performed without pause
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_361aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_361asc.mp3
  - Cage, John One [to 4th power]; Three [squared]; Four [to 4th power]; Six. Part 2, 1993-10-30, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 630-NAF 633 Tape type: TDK_SA_90 (Box 7, Audiocassette 361 Side b)
    Duration: 43:03
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_361bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_361bsc.mp3
  - Harrison, Lou, 1917-2003 Perilous chapel (1948), 1993-10-30, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 634 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 362 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 191, October 30, 1993, 4:00 p.m.
    Duration: 17:26
    Performers: Cheryl Gobbetti, flute; Arie Lipsky, violoncello; Beth Ann Breneman, harp; Jennifer Waite, percussion
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_362aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_362asc.mp3
  - Harrison, Lou, 1917-2003 Suite, violoncello, harp (1949), 1993-10-30, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 635 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 362 Side b)
    Duration: 13:15
    Performers: Arie Lipsky, violoncello; Beth Ann Breneman, harp
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_362bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_362bsc.mp3
  - Harrison, Lou, 1917-2003 Beverly's troubadour piece (1968), 1993-10-30, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 636 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 363 Side a)
    Duration: 01:39
    Performers: Beth Ann Breneman, harp; Jennifer Waite, percussion
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_363aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_363asc.mp3
  - Harrison, Lou, 1917-2003 Jahla (1972), 1993-10-30, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 637 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 363 Side b)
    Duration: 02:13
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_363bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_363bsc.mp3
  - Harrison, Lou, 1917-2003 Avolakitashvara (1976), 1993-10-30, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 638 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 364 Side a)
    Duration: 02:32
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_364aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_364asc.mp3
  - Harrison, Lou, 1917-2003 Summerfield set (1988), 1993-10-30, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 639 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 364 Side b)
    Performers: Amy Williams, piano
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_364bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_364bsc.mp3
  - Harrison, Lou, 1917-2003 Songs in the forest (1950; rev.1991), 1993-10-30, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 640 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 365 Side a)
    Performers: Lou Harrison, poet; Cheryl Gobbetti, flute; Douglas Cone, violin; Jennifer Waite, percussion; Amy Williams, piano
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_365aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_365asc.mp3
  - Woolf, Randall, 1959- Sticks and stones (1993), 1993-10-31, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 641 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 366 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 194, October 31, 1993, 2:00 p.m.
    Duration: 05:23
    Performers: Bermuda Triangle: Dora Ohrenstein, soprano; Kathleen Supove, piano; Robert Black, contrabass
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_366aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_366asc.mp3
  - Bouchard, Linda Risky (1993), 1993-10-31, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 642 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 366 Side b)
    Duration: 04:50
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_366bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_366bsc.mp3
  - Lindberg, John Terrace (1987; rev.1993), 1993-10-31, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 643 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 367 Side a)
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_367aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_367asc.mp3
  - Leach, Mary Jane He got dictators (1993), 1993-10-31, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 644 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 367 Side b)
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_367bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_367bsc.mp3
  - Rzewski, Frederic Burghers of Rostock (1992), 1993-10-31, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 645 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 368 Side a)
    Duration: 04:12
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_368aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_368asc.mp3
  - Botti, Susan People versus (1993), 1993-10-31, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 646 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 368 Side b)
    Duration: 05:38
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_368bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_368bsc.mp3
  - Valitsky, Ken So what (1993), 1993-10-31, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 647 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 369 Side a)
    Duration: 04:05
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_369aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_369asc.mp3
  - York, Wes Protest song (1993), 1993-10-31, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 648 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 369 Side b)
    Duration: 06:15
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_369bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_369bsc.mp3
  - Weir, Judith Broken branches (1992), 1993-10-31, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 649 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 370 Side a)
    Duration: 03:43
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_370aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_370asc.mp3
  - Cummings, Conrad, 1948- There is no hope for art (1993), 1993-10-31, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 650 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 370 Side b)
    Duration: 03:26
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_370bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_370bsc.mp3
  - Finnissy, Michael Blessed be (1992), 1993-10-31, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 651 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 371 Side a)
    Duration: 03:21
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_371aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_371asc.mp3
  - Wallace, Stewart Slap your neighbor's face (1989; rev.1993), 1993-10-31, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 652 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 371 Side b)
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_371bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_371bsc.mp3
  - Tan, Dun, 1957- Memorial 19 fucks (1993), 1993-10-31, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 653 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 372 Side a)
    Duration: 07:34
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_372aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_372asc.mp3
  - Daugherty, Michael, 1954- KKK (1993), 1993-10-31, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 654 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 372 Side b)
    Duration: 04:42
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_372bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_372bsc.mp3
  - Lake, Oliver, 1942- Do you know? (1993), 1993-10-31, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 655 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 373 Side a)
    Duration: 03:06
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_373aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_373asc.mp3
  - Beglarian, Eve Enough (1993), 1993-10-31, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 656 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 373 Side b)
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_373bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_373bsc.mp3
  - Ligeti, György, 1923-2006 Etudes pour piano. Nos. 1-6 (1989-1993), 1993-10-31, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 657 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 374 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 195, October 31, 1993, 5:00 p.m.
    Duration: 27:33
    Performers: Stephen Drury, piano
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_374aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_374asc.mp3
  - Rzewski, Frederic People united will never be defeated! (1976). Part 1, 1993-10-31, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 658 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 375 Side a)
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_375aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_375asc.mp3
  - Rzewski, Frederic People united will never be defeated! (1976). Part 2, 1993-10-31, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 658 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 375 Side b)
    Duration: 25:45
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_375bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_375bsc.mp3
  - Jacopo, da Bologna, active 14th century Due madrigali (14th cent.), 1993-10-31, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 659 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 376 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 196, October 31, 1993, 8:00 p.m.
    Duration: 04:35
    Performers: Carol Plantamura, voice; John Fonville, flute; Bertram Turetzky, contrabass
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_376aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_376asc.mp3
  - Harrison, Lou, 1917-2003 Ariadne (1987), 1993-10-31, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 660 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 376 Side b)
    Duration: 07:58
    Performers: John Fonville, flute; Steven Schick, percussion
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_376bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_376bsc.mp3
  - Gaburo, Kenneth Inside, a quartet for one contrabassist (1969), 1993-10-31, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 661 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 377 Side a)
    Duration: 06:57
    Performers: Bertram Turetzky, contrabass
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_377aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_377asc.mp3
  - Barkin, Elaine, 1932- De amore, 12th century love letter (1982), 1993-10-31, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 662 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 377 Side b)
    Duration: 04:34
    Performers: Carol Plantamura, voice; Bertram Turetzky, contrabass
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_377bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_377bsc.mp3
  - Ferneyhough, Brian, 1943- Superscriptio (1981), 1993-10-31, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 663 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 378 Side a)
    Performers: John Fonville, flute
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_378aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_378asc.mp3
  - Fonville, John Night dances (1993), 1993-10-31, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 664 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 378 Side b)
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_378bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_378bsc.mp3
  - Turetzky, Bertram, 1933- Reflections on Ives and Whittier (1985), 1993-10-31, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 665 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 379 Side a)
    Duration: 08:37
    Performers: John Fonville, flute; Bertram Turetzky, contrabass
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_379aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_379asc.mp3
  - Bussotti, Sylvano Sette foglie. Collage (1959), 1993-10-31, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 666 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 379 Side b)
    Performers: Carol Plantamura, voice; John Fonville, flute; Bertram Turetzky, contrabass; Steven Schick, percussion
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_379bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_379bsc.mp3
  - Górecki, Henryk Mikolaj, 1933-2010 Good night. 3rd movement (1990), 1993-11-01, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 667 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 380 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 197, November 1, 1993, 12:00 p.m.
    Performers: Katherine Soscia, soprano; Marlene Witnauer, flute; Christopher Sierzchula, piano; Jennifer Waite, percussion
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_380aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_380asc.mp3
  - Górecki, Henryk Mikolaj, 1933-2010 Four preludes, piano (1955), 1993-11-01, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 668 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 380 Side b)
    Performers: Christopher Sierzchula, piano
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_380bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_380bsc.mp3
  - Buckinx, Boudewijn, 1945- Life without principle (1993), 1993-11-01, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 669 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 381 Side a)
    Duration: 09:43
    Performers: Katherine Soscia, soprano; Marlene Witnauer, flute; Beth Ann Breneman, harp; Christopher Sierzchula, piano; percussion
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_381aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_381asc.mp3
  - Rorem, Ned, 1923- Book of hours (1975), 1993-11-01, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 670 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 381 Side b)
    Performers: Marlene Witnauer, flute; Beth Ann Breneman, harp
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_381bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_381bsc.mp3
  - Lang, David (David A.) Anvil chorus (1990), 1993-11-01, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 671 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 382 Side a)
    Performers: Steven Schick, percussion
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_382aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_382asc.mp3
  - Zorn, John, 1953- Hockey (1979), 1993-11-01, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 672 Tape type: TDK_SA_90 (Box 7, Audiocassette 383 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 198, November 1, 1993, 7:00 p.m.
    Performers: Donald Metz, Greg Millar, electric guitar; Louis de Carlo, Rick McGirr, electric keyboard; John Bacon, Jr., Marlow Wright, percussion; Stephen Drury, prompter
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_383aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_383asc.mp3
  - Zorn, John, 1953- Hsu Feng (1985), 1993-11-01, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 673 Tape type: TDK_SA_90 (Box 7, Audiocassette 383 Side b)
    Duration: 47:25
    Tape ends before piece is finished.
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_383bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_383bsc.mp3
  - Bright, Colin Many heads--Katatjuta (1993), 1993-11-02, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 674 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 384 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 199, November 2, 1993, Unknown time
    Duration: 05:11
    Unknown
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_384aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_384asc.mp3
  - Vigeland, Nils Trio (1993), 1993-11-02, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 675 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 384 Side b)
    Duration: 14:08
    Performers: Cheryl Gobbetti, flute; Paul Schlossman, oboe; Theresa Tunnicliff, clarinet; Martha Malkiewicz, bassoon; David Kuehn, trumpet
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_384bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_384bsc.mp3
  - Yamamoto, Hiroyuki, 1967- Locus regit actum III, pianos 2 (1992), 1993-11-02, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 676 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 385 Side a)
    Performers: Christopher Sierzchula, Luk', piano
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_385aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_385asc.mp3
  - De Klerk, Dirk, 1959- Dancing and waltzing (1993), 1993-11-02, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 677 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 385 Side b)
    Performers: Cheryl Gobbetti, flute; Paul Schlossman, oboe; Theresa Tunnicliff, clarinet; Martha Malkiewicz, bassoon; David Kuehn, trumpet; Douglas Cone, violin; Robert Black, contrabass; Christopher Sierzchula, piano
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_385bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_385bsc.mp3
  - De Klerk, Dirk, 1959- Theme and variations, 1993-11-02, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 678 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 386 Side a)
    Performers: Jens Barnieck, piano
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_386aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_386asc.mp3
  - Buckinx, Boudewijn, 1945- How is the moon in Buffalo these days? (1993), 1993-11-02, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 679 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 386 Side b)
    Performers: Luk', piano; Ensemble, Charles Peltz, conductor
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_386bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_386bsc.mp3
  - Buckinx, Boudewijn, 1945- Pacific (1993), 1993-11-02, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 680 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 387 Side a)
    Duration: 10:18
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_387aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_387asc.mp3
  - Bright, Colin Too many screams (1985), 1993-11-02, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 681 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 387 Side b)
    Performers: Barbara Cooper, mezzo-soprano; ensemble, Charles Peltz, conductor
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_387bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_387bsc.mp3
  - Piazzolla, Astor Contrabajissimo (Nicho) (1993), 1993-11-02, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 682 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 388 Side a)
    Performers: Ensemble, Charles Peltz, conductor
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_388aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_388asc.mp3
  - Zorn, John, 1953- For your eyes only (1989), 1993-11-03, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 683 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 389 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 200, November 3, 1993, 8:00 p.m.
    Duration: 13:42
    Performers: Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra, Jesse Levine, conductor
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_389aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_389asc.mp3
  - Williams, Amy, 1969- Morke Kammer (Dark room) (1993), 1993-11-03, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 684 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 389 Side b)
    Duration: 16:12
    Performers: Stephen Manes, piano; Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra, Jesse Levine, conductor
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_389bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_389bsc.mp3
  - Górecki, Henryk Mikolaj, 1933-2010 Symphony no. 3, op. 36 (1976). Part 1, 1993-11-03, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 685 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 390 Side a)
    Duration: 26:37
    Performers: Martha Herr, soprano; Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra, Jesse Levine, conductor
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_390aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_390asc.mp3
  - Górecki, Henryk Mikolaj, 1933-2010 Symphony no. 3, op. 36 (1976). Part 2, 1993-11-03, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 685 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 7, Audiocassette 390 Side b)
    Duration: 28:36
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_390bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_390bsc.mp3
- Reel-to-reel tapes, 1983-1993, II.; Reel 1-22
  The 22 reel to reel tapes were added to the collection after the cassette collection had been processed. All but one of these tapes were created by Buffalo public radio station, WNED. For some of the tapes, WNED recorded North American New Music Festival concerts with their own engineers and then added interviews and spoken introductions by program producer Leila Lustig. Some programs combined content from more than one North American New Music Festival concert, and one recording included content from outside the festival proper. WNED reels have been dated based on the date of the North American New Music Festival performance. The dates of production are unknown but presumably occurred shortyly after the concert dates.
  The final tape in this series is a reel-to-reel recording of the performance of Stockhausen's Mantra, also available on Cassette 63.
  The WNED tapes are placed first, chiefly in chronological order, followed by the additional recording of Stockhausen's Mantra. The contents of the reels were numbered according to placement on the reel.
  - WNED Radio Program featuring North American New Music Festival Concert 1: Part 1, 1983-04-05, 1 10-inch reel of 1/4 audio tape; 2-channel stereo., 7.5 ips Tape 1 of 2 for program. (Box 8, Reel Reel 01)
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_391_01
    Lustig, Leila
    Spoken introduction followed by interview with composer, Kenneth Sullivan